[Music]
[Applause]
Lines of text we never check.
Scroll and tap without regret.
Contract ink that's dry and cold.
Sold our souls or so we're told.
Promises they'll never keep
before we sleep. Paper walls around our
heads.
Hoping nothing will be said.
Sign your name. Just press.
Never read a word they write.
Click okay so easily.
Did you ever ask why?
Woah woah woah woah
woah woah woah.
Pages long in legal ease.
Promises beneath the fees.
Scroll right to the end. We're blind.
Stuck with say we're doing fine.
Clicking faster than we face.
Trapped in digital routines,
swept away by all the screens.
Sign your name, just press three.
Never read a word they write.
Click okay so easily.
Did you ever ask why?
Heat.
[Music]
[Applause]
Heat.
[Music]
[Applause]